While you're away
Get dressed and escape
You're quite honest
There are passwords for entry and exit here
Do you think you can escape
What do you want to do
What do I want to do
We are husband and wife
What do you think I want to do
You killed my father
Do you think I will like you
Of course I can
Jiajia
From now on
Your world will only have me
You can hate me
But I also
will make you love me beyond control
Let me go
Jiajia
We will have a new start
I will treat you well
As long as you forget the past
We will live a happy life
Yes
We could have been very happy
But why
did you do that to my father
He is my father
It was your father who courted death
He threatened me
If I didn't marry into the Ni family
he would expose my identity
and make me lose everything
Yet marrying you was not enough
He also asked me to transfer to him
10% of Zhou's company shares
Am I supposed to be
constantly held by the throat and drained of blood by him
You admit it
You are not Zhou Xubai
This was not yours originally
It was you who had evil intentions
and killed the real Zhou Xubai
And took his place